{"data":[{"question":"Something is wrong with my washing machine. I must have it ___.","a":"repairing","b":"repair","c":"repaired","d":"to repair","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Have sth done","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"When he got home, Richard found the gas ___ but the door and the windows remained ___.","a":"burning, locking","b":"burned, locking","c":"to burn, to lock","d":"burning, locked","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Catch\/ Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb (with to) :you find \/see or watch the whole action \n- Catch\/ Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb_ing : you find \/see or watch \n- Remain PP: passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"What astonished us was to see some of the villagers ___ on the ground in a prison.","a":"seated","b":"seating","c":"to be seating","d":"seat","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Catch\/ Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb (with to) :you find \/see or watch the whole action \n- Passive voice: Catch\/ Find\/ see\/ watch...+ PP","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"The speaker raised his voice but still couldn't make himself ___.","a":"to hear","b":"hear","c":"heard","d":"hearing","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Make yourself heard\/understood etc:  to cause someone or something to be in a particular state or to change to another state","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"The little girl found her teddy bear ___ under a chair.","a":"to hide","b":"hiding","c":"hidden","d":"having hidden","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Catch\/ Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb (with to) :you find \/see or watch the whole action \n- Passive voice: Catch\/ Find\/ see\/ watch...+ PP","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"The technologists in this company were made ___ fifteen hours a day.","a":"to work","b":"work","c":"worked","d":"working","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Make sbd do sth \n- Passive: be made to verb ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"The autobiography is said ___ last month.","a":"to be published","b":"to publish","c":"to have been published","d":"publish","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Be said to do something\n- Past perfect tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"When I was passing by I saw my classmates ___ frisbees on the playground.","a":"to play","b":"play","c":"played","d":"playing","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Catch\/ Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb (with to) :you find \/see or watch the whole action \n- Catch\/ Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb_ing : you find \/see or watch part of the action","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"The mothers saw their babies well ___ at the nursery.","a":"to take care of","b":"taking care of","c":"taken care of","d":"to be taken care of","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Hear\/ Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb (with to) :you find \/see or watch the whole action \n- Passive voice: - Find\/ see\/ watch...+ PP ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"},{"question":"Tell the children ___ there not to make so much noise.","a":"playing","b":"play","c":"played","d":"to play","answer":"1","explain":"\n- When a participle phrase concludes a main clause and is describing the word right in front of it, you need no punctuation to connect the two sentence parts. The pattern looks like this: main clause + participle phrase ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"11","type":"1"}]}